export let quizData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the painting that Yusuke's mother created?",
    multichoice: ['Sakura', 'Sayuri', 'Sumire', 'Satsuki'],
    answer: 'Sayuri',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the protagonist's initial Persona?",
    multichoice: ['Arsene', 'Zorro', 'Carmen', 'Captain Kidd'],
    answer: 'Arsene',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Which of the following is not a member of The Phantom Thieves?',
    multichoice: [
      'Ryuji Sakamoto',
      'Ann Takamaki',
      'Futaba Sakura',
      'Sae Niijima',
    ],
    answer: 'Sae Niijima',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'What is the name of the cafe where the protagonist lives?',
    multichoice: ['Leblanc', 'Cafe Shibuya', 'Coffee & Curry', 'Cafe DÃ´me'],
    answer: 'Leblanc',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is Morgana's codename within The Phantom Thieves?",
    multichoice: ['Panther', 'Skull', 'Oracle', 'Mona'],
    answer: 'Mona',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Who is the student council president of Shujin Academy?',
    multichoice: [
      'Makoto Niijima',
      'Haru Okumura',
      'Yusuke Kitagawa',
      'Goro Akechi',
    ],
    answer: 'Makoto Niijima',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'Which Palace ruler represents the sin of Gluttony?',
    multichoice: [
      'Kunikazu Okumura',
      'Masayoshi Shido',
      'Suguru Kamoshida',
      'Ichiryusai Madarame',
    ],
    answer: 'Kunikazu Okumura',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'What is the name of the supercomputer AI in the Futaba Palace?',
    multichoice: ['PROMETHEUS', 'Wakaba', 'Medjed', 'Mother Computer'],
    answer: 'PROMETHEUS',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'What is the name of the app that allows the Phantom Thieves to enter the Metaverse?',
    multichoice: [
      'MetaNav',
      'ThiefSpace',
      'Metaverse Navigator',
      'ShadowRealm',
    ],
    answer: 'MetaNav',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'Which of the following is not a confidant in Persona 5?',
    multichoice: [
      'Igor',
      'Sojiro Sakura',
      'Sadayo Kawakami',
      'Masayoshi Shido',
    ],
    answer: 'Masayoshi Shido',
  },
]
